{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/51622608","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622608","name":"Anita's Kitchen","address":"150 Jefferson W.","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Joeseph & Jennifer Wegrzyn","licenseNumber":"229223","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"150","coords":"-83.04654,42.32842","geojson":{"id":"51622608","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.046543428,42.328415324]},"properties":{"name":"Anita's Kitchen","owner":"Joeseph & Jennifer Wegrzyn","address":"150 Jefferson W.","zipcode":"48226","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"229223","establishmentid":"51622608","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"150","most_recent_license_date":"2023-04-14"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"3958","name":"The District Bar and Grill","address":"150 Jefferson W.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"1531","name":"TJ's Grill Works Inc","address":"150 Jefferson Ave. W.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4182","name":"Terrace Cafe","address":"150 Jefferson Ave. W.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3236","name":"Hava Java","address":"150 Jefferson W.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4186","name":"Terrace Cafe","address":"150 Jefferson W.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3299","name":"Grabba Java","address":"150 Jefferson W.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3868","name":"Wah Hoo Chinese","address":"536 Shelby","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"1477","name":"The Board Room","address":"536 Shelby","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"334","name":"Starbucks Coffee Co #2319","address":"535 Griswold St.","zipcode":null},{"establishmentid":"3583","name":"Frank's Deli in the Buhl","address":"535 Griswold St.","zipcode":"48226"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"61678","inspectionDate":"2023-02-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2023-02-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"61677","inspectionDate":"2023-02-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2023-02-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In front of","location":"DISHWASHING ROOM","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2023-03-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"58214","inspectionDate":"2022-04-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19-temp closed","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"55865","inspectionDate":"2021-09-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19-temp closed","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"54276","inspectionDate":"2021-02-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19-temp closed","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"45335","inspectionDate":"2019-02-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"2-301.14","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall clean their hands and exposed portions of their arms as specified under § 2-301.12 immediately before engaging in FOOD preparation including working with exposed FOOD, clean EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES (P) and:\n(A)     After touching bare human body parts other than clean hands and clean, exposed portions of arms; (P)\n(B)     After using the toilet room; (P)\n(C)     After caring for or handling SERVICE ANIMALS or aquatic animals as specified in ¶ 2-403.11(B); (P).\n(D)     Except as specified in ¶ 2-401.11(B), after coughing, sneezing, using a handkerchief or disposable tissue, using tobacco, eating, or drinking; (P)\n(E)     After handling soiled EQUIPMENT or UTENSILS; (P)\n(F)     During FOOD preparation, as often as necessary to remove soil and contamination and to prevent cross contamination when changing tasks; (P)\n(G)     When switching between working with raw FOOD and working with READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\n(H)     Before donning gloves for working with FOOD; (P) and\n(I)      After engaging in other activities that contaminate the hands. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Did not wash hands","subProblem":"after handling soiled equipment, surfaces, utensils","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-02-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Hands shall be washed with hot water and soap for at least 20 seconds after contamination."},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-02-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-03-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"7-102.11","violationDescription":"Working containers used for storing POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS such as cleaners and SANITIZERS taken from bulk supplies shall be clearly and individually identified with the common name of the material. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Working containers-toxics","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not labeled as to content","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-02-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."},{"violationCode":"4-901.11","violationDescription":"After cleaning and SANITIZING, EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS shall be air-dried or used after adequate draining.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Clean equipment and utensil(s)","subItem":"pots/pans","problemDescription":"Stored/stacked wet","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE AREA (DRY)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Completely air dry all items prior to storage/use."},{"violationCode":"6-403.11","violationDescription":"(A) Areas designated for EMPLOYEES to eat, drink, and use tobacco shall be located so that FOOD, EQUIPMENT, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES are protected from contamination.\n(B) Lockers or other suitable facilities shall be located in a designated room or area where contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES can not occur.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Locker(s)/employee storage area(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Contaminates","subProblem":"Single use","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Relocate to a designated area that does not contaminate items or surfaces."}]},{"inspectionid":"43075","inspectionDate":"2018-08-06T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-08-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-08-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."},{"violationCode":"3-302.12","violationDescription":"Except for containers holding FOOD that can be readily and unmistakably recognized such as dry pasta, working containers holding FOOD or FOOD ingredients that are removed from their original packages for use in the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, such as cooking oils, flour, herbs, potato flakes, salt, spices, and sugar shall be identified with the common name of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not identified","subProblem":"","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2018-08-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."},{"violationCode":"3-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Cooling shall be accomplished in accordance with the time and temperature criteria specified under § 3-501.14 by using one or more of the following methods based on the type of FOOD being cooled:  \n   (1) Placing the FOOD in shallow pans; (Pf)\n   (2) Separating the FOOD into smaller or thinner portions; (Pf)\n   (3) Using rapid cooling EQUIPMENT; (Pf)\n   (4) Stirring the FOOD in a container placed in an ice water bath; (Pf)\n   (5) Using containers that facilitate heat transfer; (Pf)\n   (6) Adding ice as an ingredient; (Pf) or\n   (7) Other effective methods. (Pf)  \n(B) When placed in cooling or cold holding EQUIPMENT, FOOD containers in which FOOD is being cooled shall be:  \n   (1) Arranged in the EQUIPMENT to provide maximum heat transfer through the       container walls; and\n   (2) Loosely covered, or uncovered if protected from overhead contamination as          specified under Subparagraph 3-305.11(A)(2), during the cooling period to facilitate    heat transfer from the surface of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly","subProblem":"Covered","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-08-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Cool items uncovered on the top shelf of cooler."}]},{"inspectionid":"41996","inspectionDate":"2018-04-23T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-202.12","violationDescription":"(A) A handwashing sink shall be equipped to provide water at a temperature of at least 38°C (100°F) through a mixing valve or combination faucet. (Pf)  \n(B) A steam mixing valve may not be used at a handwashing sink.  \n(C) A self-closing, slow-closing, or metering faucet shall provide a flow of water for at least 15 seconds without the need to reactivate the faucet.   \n(D) An automatic handwashing facility shall be installed in accordance with manufacturer's instructions.\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Lack of hot water","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-05-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hot water."},{"violationCode":"5-204.11","violationDescription":"A HANDWASHING SINK shall be located: \n(A) To allow convenient use by EMPLOYEES in FOOD preparation, FOOD dispensing, and WAREWASHING areas;  (Pf)and\n(B) In, or immediately adjacent to, toilet rooms. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"In dishwash area","location":"WAREWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-05-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hand sink in same room as dish handling."},{"violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"SIGNAGE","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2018-05-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-201.17","violationDescription":"(A) Except as otherwise allowed by law, attachments to walls and ceilings such as light fixtures, mechanical room ventilation system components, vent covers, wall mounted fans, decorative items, and other attachments shall be EASILY CLEANABLE.\n(B) In a CONSUMER area, wall and ceiling surfaces and decorative items and attachments that are provided for ambiance need not meet this requirement if they are kept clean.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wall attachment(s)","subItem":"vent covers","problemDescription":"Not easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2018-05-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be easily cleanable."},{"violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"wall(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"Easily cleanable","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2018-05-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth and easily cleanable."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622608"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}